http://www.cartercenter.org/about/terms-of-use.html

Ambassadors Circle: Gifts of $1,000 or More
Legacy Circle: Planned Gifts, Bequests, Annuities, etc.
Carter Center Terms of Use
The use of this website signifies your agreement to the Terms of Use, including the Carter Center's Privacy Statement ("Privacy Statement").
General
The Carter Center ("Center") owns and operates www.cartercenter.org, located on servers in the United States. By visiting and/or using this website, you agree to the Terms of Use ("Terms") as it is amended from time to time. These Terms contain conditions of use, disclaimers, and other provisions, some of which limit our liability to you. If you do not agree to these Terms or cannot form a legally binding contract, you are not permitted to use this website.
Use Outside of the United States
This website is available worldwide; however, use of this website may be prohibited or restricted in countries outside the United States. If you use the website from outside the United States, you do so at your own risk and are responsible for complying with the laws and regulations of the territory from which you use the website. It is your responsibility to comply with local, state, federal and international laws (including minimum age requirements) applicable to your use of this website. You may use this website solely for your own personal informational purposes. You may not use this website for any commercial purposes.
Availability of the Website
The Center reserves the right, at any time and with or without prior notice, to change, suspend, or discontinue all or any aspect of this website. Additionally, the Center reserves the right, at any time and with or without prior notice, to you to suspend or terminate your use of this website for any reason.
Submissions and Restrictions On Use
We do not control, verify, or endorse any submissions you make on this website. You agree that you are solely responsible for any submissions you make on this website and for obtaining any third party consent that is necessary for you to make such submissions. You shall not submit unlawful, defamatory, abusive, obscene, or offensive material. You agree that you will not submit anything to the website that will or may violate any law or regulation or any rights of a third party, including but not limited to copyright, trademark, intellectual property, publicity, and/or privacy rights.
You agree that you shall not place false or misleading information on this website or upload any viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time bombs, or other computer programs that may interfere with the proper operation of this website.
Copyright and Trademark; Your Usage
Unless expressly noted otherwise, all materials on this website are protected by copyright, trademarks, service marks, and/or other intellectual property rights held by the Center, its initiatives, affiliates, or other parties that have allowed the Center to use their materials. All rights not expressly granted are reserved.
Provided you comply with these Terms, you are permitted to use this website for your personal, non-commercial purposes. You are not permitted to reproduce or distribute this website or to use it for commercial purposes. If you would like to reproduce, distribute, or use any materials on this website in any manner that is not expressly permitted by these Terms, please submit a request for permission to do so to info@cartercenter.org.
Digital Millennium Copyright Act
The Center attempts to respond to claims of copyright infringement in a timely manner. If you believe this website (or any material contained on this website) is infringing your copyright, please send the following information to info@cartercenter.org:
A description of your copyrighted work, including the United States Copyright Office registration number
A description of the material that you believe may be violating your copyright
Your address, telephone number, and email address
A statement that you have a good faith belief that the use of the copyright is not authorized
A statement that the information you have provided is accurate
Links to Other websites
Links on this website may connect you to other websites that are not related to the Center or under its control and whose use is not subject to these Terms or the Privacy Statement. The appearance of links to other sites does not imply an affiliation or endorsement to any of those websites or to any entities associated with or supporting any of those websites, and you access other websites at your own risk. You are encouraged to review the policies and terms of use associated with any linked website closely before using or submitting information to the linked website.
Donations
All donations made using this website must be made in compliance with federal, state, and local laws relating to charitable contributions, including but not limited to the U.S. Patriot Act and the IRS Tax Code, as they may be amended from time to time. Please read the Carter Center’s Donor Privacy Statement.
Privacy Policy
The Center is committed to helping you understand how information collected from your computer is used. This information is contained in our Privacy Statement, which governs the collection of personal information on or through this website and the use and disclosure of such personal information. If you are located outside the United States, please note that the information you provide will be transferred to the United States. The laws of the United States may not provide the same level of legal data protection as the country from which you access the website. By using the website and sharing personal information with us, you consent to and authorize such transfer and the use and processing by us of information as described in the Privacy Statement.
Modification
The Center may and will in its sole discretion modify any of these Terms, including our Privacy Statement, at any time, for any reason, by making changes to the Terms. Your continued use of this website, after such modifications, constitutes acceptance of such modifications and your agreement to be bound by the modified Terms and/or Privacy Statement.
Disclaimer of Warranties
THE CENTER DOES NOT GUARANTEE THAT THE FUNCTIONS AND CONTENTS CONTAINED IN OR ON THE WEBSITE WILL BE WITHOUT ERRORS, THAT THIS WEBSITE WILL BE FREE OF VIRUSES, OR THAT ANY WEBSITE DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, EVEN IF THE CENTER IS AWARE OF THEM. THE CENTER MAKES NO REPRESENTATION AS TO THE COMPLETENESS, ACCURACY, OR TIMELINESS OF ANY INFORMATION CONTAINED ON THE WEBSITE. YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE AND ITS CONTENT IS AT YOUR RISK. THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ALL CONTENT, IS PROVIDED “AS IS,” “WITH ALL FAULTS,” AND “AS AVAILABLE.” TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, THE CENTER EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL EXPRESS AND IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT.
Limitation of Liability
The Center does not assume any responsibility, and shall not be liable for, any damages to, or viruses that may infect, your computer, telecommunication equipment, or other property caused by or arising from your use of this website. IN NO EVENT WILL THE CENTER OR ITS AFFILIATES BE LIABLE TO ANY PARTY FOR ANY INDIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THOSE RESULTING FROM LOST PROFITS, LOST DATA, OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) ARISING OUT OF THE USE, INABILITY TO USE, OR THE RESULTS OF USE OF THIS WEBSITE, ANY LINKED WEBSITE, OR THE MATERIALS, INFORMATION, OR SERVICES CONTAINED OR OFFERED AT ANY OR ALL SUCH SITES, WHETHER BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY AND WHETHER OR NOT ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY DO NOT APPLY TO THE EXTENT PROHIBITED BY LAW. PLEASE REFER TO YOUR LOCAL LAWS FOR ANY SUCH PROHIBITIONS. IN THE EVENT OF ANY PROBLEM WITH THIS WEBSITE, YOU AGREE THAT YOUR SOLE REMEDY IS TO CEASE USING THE WEBSITE.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless the Center, its affiliates, initiatives, and members of its and its affiliates’ Boards, employees, contractors, licensors, and agents from any and all losses, damages, liabilities, fines, penalties, costs, and expenses of every nature incurred by any of them in connection with any claim, damage, suit, settlement, or loss related to your unlawful, unauthorized, and /or inappropriate use of this website or any materials contained on this website or your violation of any of the Terms.
Jurisdiction
Any dispute rising from these Terms, including our Privacy Statement, shall be construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the State of Georgia without regard to the principles of conflicts of law. You acknowledge and agree that the courts of the State of Georgia shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any and all such disputes, that you shall submit to that jurisdiction and those courts, and that you expressly waive any and all rights you may have, or that may hereafter arise, to contest the propriety of such choice of jurisdiction and venue, including issues of forum non conveniens.
The Center will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order or subpoena requesting or directing the Center to disclose the identity of anyone violating these Terms and/or applicable law.
Additional Terms
If any provision of these Terms is held to be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, that provision will be deemed severable and will not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions. Section headings in these Terms are for convenience only and have no legal or contractual effect. This Section of the Terms, and the Sections entitled “Disclaimer of Warranties,” “Limitation of Liability,” “Indemnification” and “Jurisdiction” shall survive any expiration or termination of these Terms.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about these Terms, including any particular provision or our Privacy Statement, please send us an email.
Updated: April 21, 2017
Donate Now
Sign Up For Email
Please sign up below for important news about the work of The Carter Center and special event invitations.
First Name:
Last Name:
Spam Control Text:
Please leave this field empty
Now, we invite you to Get Involved
Back To Top
